Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. National Jobs With Justice
  - National Campaigns
    - GE Contract Fight, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Global Exchange, 1996-2001 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Good Jobs First, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - GGJ, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Grassroots Initiative Policy Project (GRIPP), 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Grassroots Leadership: Community Assets Campaign, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Grassroots Leadership: Privatization Research Project, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Grassroots Policy Research, 1995-1999 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Gray Panthers, 1994-2000 (Box 25, Folder 31-32)
    - Helena Labs, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Helena Labs (CWA), 1999 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Highlander Research + Education Center - Reports, 1995-2001 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - ILWU Solidarity, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - IMF - Fred Azcarate Speech, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Immigrant Legislation, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Immigrant Organizing, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Institution for America's Future, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Institute for Democratic Renewal + Project Change Anti-Racism Initiative, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Initiative for Policy Studies: Progressive Challenge, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - IPS: Letelier-Moffitt Awards, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - International Conference on Free Trade Unions, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - International Human Rights Law Group, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - International Mission Church, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - JEDI for Women, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Fund for Justice, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Jews United for Justice, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Job is a Right Campaign, 1994-07 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Jobs For All Coalition, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Jobs Now Coalition - Minnesota, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Jubilee, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Just Cause, 1996-08-30 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Just Economics, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - "Justice Do It Nike!" - Oregon Coalition, 1996-08 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Justice for Janitors, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Kentuckian for the Commonwealth, 1981-1996 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Kentucky-Mexico Worker Exchange, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 41-42)
    - The Kopkind Colony, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Labor Cartoons + Citizen Soldier, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - National Committee on Pay Equality, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Labor Council for Latin America Advancement (LCLAA), 1996-05 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Labor Heritage - Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Labor History Tour Bus/Harmonica Hinds Contract (Chicago Annual Meeting), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Labor Institute - Corporate Power + the American Dream, 1995-03-1995-04 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Study of Job Growth in America, 1998-12 (Box 26, Folder 28-29)
    - JWJ Slideshow: NAFTA, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Ohio NAFTA Documents, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - NAFTA/GATT - Citizens Trade Campaigns, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 32-33)
    - NAFTA - File #2, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 34-35)
    - No NAFTA for the Americas!, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - NAFTA and Ohio, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - CAFTA, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - One on One Shop NAFTA, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - National Campaign for Jobs and Income, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - National Coalition for the Homeless, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - National Employment Law Project, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - National Family Farm Coalition, 1993-2001 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - National Farm Worker Ministry, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - National Immigration Forum, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - National Immigration Law Center, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker + Human Rights in CA, 1995-2001 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - National Labor-Community Coalition for Public Works Jobs, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - NLRB - Workplace Organizational Rights, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - National Priorities Project: Are you winning or losing?, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - National Rainbow Coalition Labor Network News, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - National Toxics Campaign, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - New Directions Worker Education Center, 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - NTUI, 2005-01-07 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - S 26 Materials: Org. Kit, Media Kit, Report, Grid, Top 11, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - S26, 2000-09-26 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Extra Articles S26, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - The NW Federation of Community Organizations: NW Directions, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - NPP Report + Briefing, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Overnite, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 16-17)
    - Overnite, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Overnite, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Privatization vs. The Public Interest, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Respect DC, 2012-2014 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Retail Campaigns, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Ruiz Foods Scripts, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - S26 4-Pager, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - S26 Organizing Kit, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - S26 Report + Press, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Teamster Appeal for JWJ, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 26-27)
    - Unite - Guess Campaign, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Unity, 2010-2013 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Verizon Info, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - CWA BA/Verizon Campaign, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 31-32)
    - JWJ + Teamsters UPS Strike, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - US West Strike, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Verizon, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Verizon Campus Org Kit, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - V2W, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - VZ, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - VZ, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Voice at Work Presentation, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Voice at Work Presentation, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - SF JWJ Walmart/Retail, 2014 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Walmart Free NYC, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Walmart, Fall (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Walmart - UFCW, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Walmart, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Walmart, 2013-2014 (Box 51, Folder 22-23)
    - Walmart. This. Must. Stop. Poster, 2005 (Mapcase folder 1)
    - Workers' Rights Info, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - 50 Years is Enough, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Immigrant Workers' Freedom Ride - Student Org Kit, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Immigrant Workers' Freedom Ride 4-Pager, Fall (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Kentucky-Sonora Worker Exchange, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Workers' Rights are Human Rights Educational, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Right to Organize 4-Pager, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Welfare Reform Comic, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - AT&T Mobilization, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Fall MOB Against G. Bush, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - UPS, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Welfare Reform, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Interfaith, 1997-2003 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Living Wage Packet and General Info., 1999 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - New Economy, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - GE, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Right to Organize 4-Pager, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Cullman Venture Inc., 2000 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Living Wage Campaigns, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - New Voices Media Project, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Discount Foundation Globalization, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Global Justice Strategy Session, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - NCJIS, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Phoenix Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Bill Usury Labor Management Relations, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - State Budget Crises, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - World Economic Forum/World Social Forum, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Justice for Janitors, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - NAFFE, 2001-2004 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - World Social Forum, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - HERE-HOTELS, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Work @ Work Freedom to Choose a Union, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Right to Organize Materials, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Columbia, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Employee Free Choice Act - ARAW, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Peabody Complex, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Reforming The H-2B Guest Program, 2012-2015 (Box 33, Folder 39)
      Includes CDs.
    - Bank Workers, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - WYE River, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Guestworkers Data, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Healthcare
      - HCAD, 2001-2003 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Rights Resource Directory and HC Action Toolkit, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Health Care Emergency Drive, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 29-30)
      - Health Care - Jobs with Justice, 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Health Care Action Toolkit, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Health Care 4 All 4-Pager, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - 2004 Action Health Week (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Healthcare, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Healthcare Affiliated Organizations, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Putting Families First Advisory Council, 2015 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Healthcare Clips, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Just Healthcare Misc., 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - JWJ Mailings, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - JWJ Healthcare Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Jobs With Justice Healthcare Reform Spanish + English, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Jobs With Justice Healthcare Mobilization, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Jobs With Justice Healthcare Action Week, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Healthcare Action Week, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Emergency Drive for Healthcare, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Emergency Drive for Healthcare, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Healthcare Clips, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Press Conference Call May 1 at 1PM and Media Kit, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Healthcare Action Wk 6/3 - 9/91, 1991-06-03-1991-09 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Newspaper Clippings, Healthcare Protest 1991 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Old Healthcare, 1991-1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Healthcare Single Payer Survey, Spring (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - CHS Lobby Kit, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Univ. HC. Strat. Conference, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Healthcare Visit Kit, 1992-03 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Healthcare Clips, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Jobs With Justice Healthcare, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Bad Bills Healthcare, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - PRE GDD Misc., 1994 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - CHS Organizations Use of Our Materials, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - JWJ HCAD (Healthcare Action Day) Coordinators, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Sign-On Letters Healthcare, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - National Healthcare Action Wk (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - June HCAD, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Consumer Coalition for Quality Healthcare, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Ontario Health Coalition, 2000-06 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Rockefeller Proposal, 2000-11 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Healthcare Delegation, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Feb. Lobby Kit Healthcare, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Inventories, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Healthcare, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Pledge for Health Care Reform, 1994 (Mapcase folder 1)
        Six pledges signed by congressmen Gerry Studds, James Clyburn, Bill Richardson, Sidney Yates, William Coyne, and George Miller. Includes photocopy of pledge signed by Alan Wheat.
      - JWJ Rally poster, 1987 (Mapcase folder 1)
        Poster in Spanish for July 29, 1987 rally at Miami Beach Convention Center. 2 copies.
    - National Day of Action
      - Healthcare News Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Health Care Action Day, 1990-10-03 (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
      - Health Care - Action Day, 1994-02-17 (Box 12, Folder 25-26)
      - All We Wanted Was a Union, 1994-09 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Anti-Contract on America, 1995-06 (Box 13, Folder 78)
      - Corporate Greed Flyers, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - Day of Action - Corp Greed Event Reports, Media, etc., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - June Day of Action, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Media Relations Kit, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - National Day of Action Corp Greed - Coordinators List Forms, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - National Day of Action Against Corporate Greed, 1996-09 (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
      - "An Alternative Tashlich", 1997 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - Coordinating Committee Weekly Updates, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Day of Action - Media Plan, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Day of Action Org Kit, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Field Organizers, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Gannett Action Organizing Materials, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Gannett Actions Local Contacts, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - General Day of Action, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Grid + Contacts, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Labor Pamphlets, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - National Day of Action, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - National Day of Welfare Mailer, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Outreach - Day of Action, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Press Clips 2, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - Press Packet, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Religious Community Packet, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Sprint, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Sprint Action Organizing Materials, 1997-07-14 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Welfare Day of Action, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Welfare Day of Action: Personal Stories, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Welfare Day of Action: Resources, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Day of Action, 1997-06-12 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Gannett Day of Action Follow-Up, 1997-06-12 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Gannett Day of Action Press Clips, 1997-06-12 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Sprint Action: Literature, 1997-07-14 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Sprint Actions Coordinators, 1997-07-14 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Sprint Actions: Press Clips, 1997-07-14 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Albany, NY, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Atlanta, GA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Augusta, ME, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Austin, TX, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Baltimore, MD, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Bellingham, WA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Bloomington, IN, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Boise, ID, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Boston, MA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Buffalo, NY, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Charleston, SC, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Charleston, WV, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Chicago, IL, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Columbia, SC, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Dallas, TX, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Denver, CO, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Des Moines, IA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - Detroit, MI, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Duluth, MN, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Eugene, OR, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Framingham, MA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Harrisburg, PA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Honolulu, HI, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - Indianapolis, IN, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - Jackson, MS, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - Knoxville, TN, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - Lakeland, FL, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Lincoln, NE, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Little Rock, AR, 1997-12 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Los Angeles, CA, 1997-12 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Louisville, KY, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Milwaukee, WI, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Missoula, MT, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Nashville, TN, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - New York, NY, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Northampton, MA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Oakland/SF, CA, 1997-12 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Patterson, NJ, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Philadelphia, PA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Phoenix, AZ, 1997-12 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Pittsburgh, PA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Providence, RI, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - Raleigh/Durham, NC, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Richmond, VA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Salem, MA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Salt Lake City, UT, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - San Antonio, TX, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - San Diego, CA, 1997-12 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Seattle, WA, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - St. Louis, MO, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      - Tallahassee, FL, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - Tulsa, OK, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Welfare, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 80)
      - Welfare Day of Action, 1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Day of Action Media, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Day of Action Resource Materials #3, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - National Day of Action for Welfare Justice! Media Kit, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - National Day of Action for Welfare Justice! Media Kit, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - National Day of Action for Welfare Justice! Media Kit, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - National to Locals, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Press Clips, 1997-12-10 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Briefing RSVP - NPP Report Release, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - June Day of Action + Jan - June Files, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 7-9)
      - NPP Report + Requests, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Public Job Creation: Meeting with C.C.C., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Release Cities Conference Call - NPP Report Release, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Report Release → Media Reports, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
      - AFL-CIO: Right to Organize Day of Action, 1998-06-24 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - AFL-CIO Town Hall Meetings, 1998-12 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - NPP Report Press Clips, 1998-12-08 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - NPP Report Release, 1998-12-08 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Rhode Island, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - April 16th, 2000-04 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - A16 - April 16 Rally, 2000-04-16 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - A16 Press Clips, 2000-04-16 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Bill of Rights Day of Action - Org. Kit, Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Union Tracking Files
    - Tracking, 2001-04 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tracking, 2001-05 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Tracking, 2002-05 (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
    - Union Campaign Summaries, Emails, and Union Tracking Forms, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Emails and Union Tracking Forms, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
    - Tracking-Database-Outline, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
    - American Federation of Musicians Support Tejano Advancement in Recording (STAR), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - American Federation of Teachers/Teachers, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - American Postal Workers Union, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Carpenters, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Unions - Communications Workers of America Organizing Manual, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Communications Workers of America - Talking Union, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Communications Workers of America - Missouri State Workers Union, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Communications Workers of America, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - (International Union of Electrical Workers) Communications Workers of America, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Hearings, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - HERE, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Identity Access Management, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1995-2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - International Longshore and Warehouse Union, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - International Union of Operating Engineers, 2002-04-04 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Laborers International Union of North America, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Laborers International Union of North America, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Laborers International Union, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - National Farmers Union, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - National Organization of Legal Services Workers, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - United Child Care Union, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - PACE - Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical, and Energy Workers, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - PACE - Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical, and Energy Workers, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Pineros y Campesinos Unidos del Noroeste/Farm Worker Union, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Roofers and Waterproofers, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Service Employees International Union, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Service Employees International Union, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Service Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Teamster Updates - (FAX), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Temporary Workers Union-Cleveland, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - United Auto Workers, 1992-2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - United Auto Workers, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - United Food and Commercial Workers, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - United Food and Commercial Workers, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - United Mine Workers of America Journal, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - UNITE, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - UNITE, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Union-United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - United Steelworkers of America, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - United Steelworkers of America, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Sarita Gupta Files
    - Health Care, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Jobs with Justice Documents, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Local Coalition Development, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Jobs with Justice Strategic, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Jobs with Justice Documents, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - S26 Localize the Movement of Global Justice, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - New Trade Union Initiatives Documents, 2000-2007 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Free Trade Area of America, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Information of Free Trade of the Americas Agreement, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Leverage Wheel, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Jobs with Justice Strategic Plan, 2003-05 (Box 28, Folder 11)